Do we know where the accessory class is?
I know it says here that it's said that it doesn't offer a comment.
I would call it the regular meeting of the Modesty Council for May 23rd, 2022.
Number two, Mr. Theoath for East Step, Brown East Step, North East Ward 1, and Kevin Nucle North West Ward 2.
Do you have any questions?
Yes.
I would stand in there.
I'll stand on those left and left.
What is the approval for you?
Do you need your money?
Do you got a ring on your hand?
I need your hand.
Kevin O'Brien East Step.
Do you solemnly swear or firm?
You solemnly swear or firm.
Then I will support Obey and defend the Constitution of the United States.
And the Constitution of the State of the Portland.
And the Constitution of the State of Oklahoma.
And then I will not know when we receive correctly or indirectly.
And if any of us are valuable things.
If any money or other valuable things.
For the performance or non-performance of any actor duty.
For the performance or I'm on performance of any actor duty.
Other than the compensation allowed by law.
Other than the compensation.
I further swear or firm.
Then I will respectfully discharge.
According to the best of my ability.
The duty said my office during such time as I have a member.
The duty said my office as time as I am a member.
As a lie in the city council.
And the board of trustees.
Of the my and especially you.
Of the city of the city of my.
Of the city of my.
Thank you.
You.
I did.
Three action on resolution 22 to 0 7.
Should we the same motion.
Make same motion.
I made earlier.
All second earlier.
You step.
I.
Davis.
I'm staying.
I.
Four city manager communications.
I have nothing.
Five.
Germany.
I moved.
Second.
No.